Jeffrey de Mesa

Designer and Web Developer

CONTACT

PHONE

+6390 8400 4955

EMAIL ADDRESS

jeffdemesa96@gmail.com

EDUCATION

RIZAL TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY

BS in Information and Communications Technology SY: 2012 - 2017

RIZAL HIGH SCHOOL

Secondary School SY: 2008 - 2012

STAR OF HOPE CHRISTIAN SCHOOL

Primary School SY: 2002 - 2008

SKILLS

INDUSTRY APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

















PROTOTYPING & DESIGN TOOLS









DATABASE APPLICATIONS





STATEMENT

I am a developer and a designer with a 7+ years of experience in creating user experience designs, mockups, high-fidelity prototypes, and working user interface application. I am also taking a path on backend stuff to have a grasp to build application from both ends.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Sulzer Inc. / September 2022 - Present • 1 year+

Development responsibilities that I hold:

- WordPressTheme
- Gutenberg Blocks
- PHP backend
- Different email provider theme development (Mailchimp, Pardot, HubSpot, etc)
- Maintenance of existing websites.

SENIOR WEB ENGINEER AND DESIGNER

Taxumo / August 2017 - Present • 5 years+

I am responsible for the following:

- user interface design
- database management
- feature development
- RESTful APIs development
- C# backend

Responsible also for the maintenance of web application of Taxumo. I make sure that they have their user has the best experience on overall usability of the app.

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER AND DESIGNER

Freelance / August 2016 - Present • 7 years+

I do some freelance projects from various clients in my spare time mostly after my morning shift job. I do some UI designs, mockups, high-fidelity prototypes, web application developments, and WordPress.

FREELANCE WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Tribe Limited / April 2017 - August 2017 • 5mos

I engage to a wordpress website development contract to this company. I also perform periodic maintenance to which is availed as another contract after the project development.